# **IMRAN MAQBOOL**

#### **ABOUT ME**

As a CAD CAM Designer with a creo parametric, SW and Design X background in manufacturing industry, accompanying with a diploma of associate engineering technology focused in mechanical, I have extensive experience of 3d scanning, 3D modeling, 2D drafting.

### **PERSONAL INFORMATION**

<u>Father Name</u>: Muhammad Maqbool <u>EMAIL</u>: emranmaqbool55@gmail.com

<u>Date Of Birth</u>: 25-Nov-2002 <u>GENDER</u>: Male

**CNIC NO.**: 42401-6651193-3 **PHONE & WHATSAPP NO.**: +(92) 347-0355927

ADDRESS: Plot # 1130 Street # 13 Block C/3 Ghousia chowk gulshan-e-bahar orangi town karachi.

## **KEY SKILL**

- Creo Parametric
- SolidWorks
- AutoCAD
- Geomagic Design x
- MS Office

## **EDUCATION**

- Bachelor of Science in Mechanical Engineering Technology (Continue)
  - Indus university faculty of science and technology.
- Diploma of Associate Engineering in Mechanical

Government college of technology.

• Intermediate ( Pre-Engineering )

SM government science college.

Matriculation

AL Habib grammar school

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Kohinoor Metals

Automotive Industry

**CAD/CAM Designer** 

Dec 2022 - Present

- 3D modeling & 2D drafting with creo Parametric & SW.
- Reverse engineering with geomagic design x.
- 3D scanning hands on experience in Handyscan 3S/Zscanner 700.
- Sheet metal process dies and pressure die casting mold assembly design and drawings, scale layout drawings.
- CNC progarming with creo parametric hand on experience of tool path generation.

Burraq Engineerings

Automotive Industry

**Quality Inspector** 

Feb 2022 - Dec 2022

- Inprocess Inspection.
- Final Inspection.

• Dawood Engineerings

Automotive Industry

**Quality Inspector** 

Aug 2021 - Feb 2022

- Inprocess inspection.
- Final inspection.